things that they have to boy because I
have to acquire personal free
electricity that's not free running a
business it's cost you for your business
ever that's not free so these
are here throwing you sort of brings
something free to some people the best
they can in the ultimate in but it's not
it's not free to them and it won't
probably be free to you
you won't get so really the reason I was
right
anytime this Dodger yeah we're with this
trying to get free without they are in
it and just put a feed on on the end of
it to get a feed out of it well we did
for how long as you said we were making
a mistake some boy you have that problem
that you have to do later well now we
charge it's a it's a matter if you win
to give okay go at the obese they can
they got to keep the prize as far as I
can see they're gonna keep whatever they
do do for freedom everything else you're
gonna keep it down which you'll be a
kickback in another way because they
will get some credibility and they get
some other people coming back it'll
always be feedback and they might on
tell some other stuff and they might
learn some more stuff on you people
turning up and now about stuff that
they're doing so they'll accumulate
accumulate knowledge as well and that
knowledge say that they then can pass on
to other people as well freely in so on
and if there's some really really
technical stuff where is something well
it's very some people are going to have
to come into the business here and
actually pay to at some stage to listen
because there's people out there who
have been paid to talk in that would be
able technical stuff an event freedom
stuff better
so people are willing is to give a few
facts to actually listen to somebody hey
look at put it down what's his name
Suzuki yeah Suzuki I don't agree I mean
because of his evolution where he saw
the things because I'm on creation sorry
please
but I got judging on that I just he's
doing anything he does a hell of a lot
of good but now he's not doing a hell of
a lot what he's doing he's doing a hell
I'm talking which is probably hopefully
bringing in a whole lot of you know
congregation to new people thinking on
different lines so that's a really good
fender and a pat on the back for you but
they planned him a lot of money to turn
up and they're taking him on and there's
nothing wrong with that and he goes to
meetings and he might not be charged in
the hell of a lot I'm not running down
on that I would you say he is charging
your own contribution to even there's
still something but he has to get around
once
yes sir this is justification to stop
saying he's doing wrong but he's out
there now doing a hell of a lot of
talking to try and bring paper like
using this summer so debate
late but he's now Big Valley to tour
restriction from doing the whole load of
anything else so everyone come down to
these fellas here to get my baby very
soon when they came I might enough okay
one gallon token they put on a small
demonstration that they're comfy but I
love it open you want to do that they
need to learn
for us
probably gonna tell them for food ready
yeah yes I think we come to probably as
bad as much as all but maybe you should
come see these guys no thank you we're
not allowed you to do money
and wasn't all we've got a debate today
how do I give her Steve Shoe Diaries
you guys ain't come in here Bobby means
I think they can mine we're up to
bidding that telling me Charlie
and I'm still not against the paper with
a big dollars in there you know so tell
me Charlie maybe there's just I really
start analyzing people before I start
talking business it's not this way to be
sure there were these sugar for
something or kicking me out
ensure that before they walk in the door
because it could be the champion
anyway magic thanks Jeff okay
see yourself another time probably okay
they might be interested in diversity
cities proven there's a sale of oil just
as proven habit they dive in theory of
evolution and freshness
jesseman so you have to even conceive
the other thought I don't even see a lot
of people who put it out the way that
they said hey I'm the format's in the
earth you know they're this time you
know fossils stuff that ever you go yeah
but all that they are deep it down there
you go check out some of the right stuff
flipping as it was laid down and
everything else will slide down and
rolls over the engine but actually what
you think is he all this is early the
youngest and what's the youngest is he
obviously just upside down and now it's
like down what they said is you're
unwary
and then you want with the creation can
turn the world upside down anyway
everything on top got shut down
underneath with the big flood turned it
all up and turned it all around
it's tough she's alive